





Summary

Jump to Section

As a business analyst have experience in managing and delivering products/services for customers across various domains, proficient in customer interactions and working in collaboration with all the stakeholders to develop/build quality products.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Work Experience

- 3i Infotech as Business Analyst Jun 2019 to Till Date
 - 1. Contributed towards the creation of a flagship product in the agri-banking sector enabling the end users to trade in agriculture commodities through future contracts.
 - 2. Conducted requirement elicitation through workshops and one to one interactions with business stakeholders.
 - Worked on preparation of documents such as Business Requirement Document, Functional Design Document etc. across the lifecycle of the project for the development of the products.
 - 4. Contributed towards preparation of Mock-Ups/Wireframes of Web based application and Android app.
 - 5. Experience in conducting impact analysis for incoming Change requests against the original scope.
 - 6. Have conducted UAT and SIT in collaboration with the customer.
 - 7. Assisted QA team in preparation of end-user centric test scenarios and test cases.
- RISTA MOBILITY as Technical Consultant -ERP May 2018 to May 2019
 - 1. Contributor towards devising Strategies and Product road-map for the SaaS products.
 - 2. Worked with the Core team to devise go to market strategy to achieve better market share.
 - 3. Conducted POCs for the SaaS products to the potential clients to enable their digital transformation journey.
 - 4. Provided support for the sales team through RFP (Request For Proposal) preparation Scope Management.
 - 5. Build and source collateral including Product requirements, user stories, case studies and wire-frames.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Dayananda Sagar College Of Engineering, Bangalore in 2015

PG: MBA/PGDM (IT and Analytics) from Institute for Technology and Management (ITM) in 2018

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:
Mcrosoft Office and Advance Excel Certification
Data Visualization with Tableau Specialization - UC Davis
Applied Data Science with Pubes Specialization - University of Making



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Advance Excel	
Agile Business Analysis	
JIRA	
Azure DevOps	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓	
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓	

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Blockchain based Trading Platform Client: Cropdata Technologies Private Limited Nature of Employment: Full Time

Nature of Employment: Full 11m Project Location: Bangalore Role: Other

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Team Size: 25

Duration: Aug 2019 - Till Date

Skill Used: Business Analysis, Requirements Elicitation, Product Management, User experience, Data Analysis,

Stakeholders Management, Documentation Role Description: Business Analyst

Project Details: Developed a flagship product in the banking sector enabling the end users to trade in agriculture

commodities through future contracts.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.